{
    "subject": "resource/Kazi_Jalil_Abbasi",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Kazi Jalil Abbasi was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.930629312992096,
            "question": "Where was Kazi Jalil Abbasi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9187535047531128,
            "question": "Is Kazi Jalil Abbasi Indian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082032799720764,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Kazi Jalil Abbasi's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.749485433101654,
            "question": "What country is Kazi Jalil Abbasi from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6859133839607239,
            "question": "Where did Kazi Jalil Abbasi grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6665574312210083,
            "question": "What are some significant events that occurred in India during Kazi Jalil Abbasi's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6436126828193665,
            "question": "What is Kazi Jalil Abbasi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.62840336561203,
            "question": "What impact has India had on Kazi Jalil Abbasi's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5677916407585144,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from India who share a similar background with Kazi Jalil Abbasi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4153285026550293,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Kazi Jalil Abbasi's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kazi Jalil Abbasi was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6989_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from India who share a similar background with Kazi Jalil Abbasi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6989_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has India had on Kazi Jalil Abbasi's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6989_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Kazi Jalil Abbasi known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6989_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6989_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Kazi Jalil Abbasi was born in Bayara, Uttar Pradesh, India. Therefore, the statement \"Kazi Jalil Abbasi was born in India\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}